<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Orphanage</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close</string>
    <string name="error_message">Oops! Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="address">The Chavadi Child Welfare Society\n(poor students ashram)
        \n\nPlot No. 224, Telecom Nagar(Extn.),
        Gachibowlli,\nHyderabad-500032,\nPh:040-65301431</string>

    <string name="aboutus">Our orphan children are the very heart of our mission.
        Though all come from destitute or desperate situations, some as far away as Orissa,
        Sikkim or Assam, they are all cared for as members of our large family and treated
        as the beautiful individuals that they are. As with all children worldwide,
        each boy and girl comes to us with their own unique dreams, passions and talents.
        Our job is to develop the whole person, not simply feed and clothe a needy child.
        On some basic levels, our orphan children are given three nutritious meals
        each day as well as morning and afternoon tea—with the occasional snacks
        such as ice cream, chips and “gol guppa” (a kid favorite) added just for fun.
        Meals are eaten as a family in our dining room where children,
        staff and volunteers come together to give thanks.</string>

    <string name="ourmission">To fulfill the basic needs for Orphanages across India.
        \n\nTo fulfill the basic needs like Food, Shelter,Clothing and Education for Kids
        in Orphanages across India.\n\nThe Good Shepherd Agricultural Mission is an independent,
        non-governmental, social development organization that has been providing
        support to those in need. ‘The Mission’ works in an array of areas,
        support to lepers, vocational training, education, disaster relief etc.
        but it’s primary focus is the care and protection of orphan children.
        The Mission works hard to provide a loving home and family for every child
        in its care working hard to promote family relationships and impart a spirit of
        responsibility in every member of the organization.</string>

    <string name="ourwork">Our main area of work is fulfilling the needs of the Orphanages.
        On reguler basis we post the requirements from the Orphanages and you can process
        requirements of your choice. Apart from the listed requirements you can donate
        in any other form and also financially aid these Orphanages.</string>

</resources>
